Hey, so I'm going to be as respectful about this as possible, but the truth is your claim
is completely bad faith.
You do not care about being anti-crime.
You yourself are pro-crime.
Your side is pro-crime because you're a progressive.
How am I pro-crime?
So I'll give you an example, right?
So your side, not Donald Trump, has passed a series of laws in California.
Let's go with California.
It's where we are right now.
It's where I'm from.
I don't know.
Are you from California?
No.
Okay.
So you're a progressive.
You're completely progressive, just passed a law that limits sex offender registration
to 10 years.
It was life before.
That's pro-crime.
The legislature in California, which is progressives again, has passed a law that says the voter-induced
three-strike law is no longer absolute.
If someone attempts to murder someone, stab someone on three separate occasions, a judge
now does not have to give them life.
That's a progressive law.
That is not.
That is pro-crime.
You support that, don't you?
I actually don't support sex offenders coming off a list.
I think they should be on for life.
Okay.
So you disagree with progressives.
Hold on.
You and I both agree that sex offending is a bad thing, especially child sex offending,
right?
It seems like you and I agree on that.
I agree on that.
The legislature of California doesn't.
So I'm not here to debate the legislature of California.
I'm here to debate Donald Trump being pro-crime, and I'm saying that Donald Trump was friends
with Ghislaine Maxwell.
When Ghislaine Maxwell, who's the worst child sex trafficker of our lifetime, she's serving
in the 20s.
Do you know Ghislaine Maxwell?
Yeah, she's actually not.
Jeffrey Epstein's the worst sex trafficker.
He's dead.
I'm talking about people alive right now.
It's interesting, though, you didn't use his name, right?
Wouldn't he be the one who did this?
Oh, great.
Jeffrey Epstein.
Jeffrey Epstein, before he died, did an interview with Michael Wolff.
He's on tape.
I don't know if you've heard the tape.
He says, my closest friend was Donald Trump.
I was his closest friend.
Elon Musk.
I'm not sure if you've heard of him.
He tweeted recently that Donald Trump's name is in the Epstein files.
And Ghislaine Maxwell, who was the right-hand woman of Jeffrey Epstein, when she was on
trial for child sex offending, which you and I are opposed to, Donald Trump stood up and
said, good luck to her.
I wish her well.
So, yeah, that makes him pro-crime and pro-criminal if he's being soft on child sex traffickers.
Well, you just said they were his friends.
Like Epstein.
He's clearly saying something.
He said he was friends with Epstein.
You haven't seen the videos?
They danced together, partied together.
Yeah, yeah.
It's a guy.
He's not supported the pedophilia part.
The only people supporting pedophilia are the left.
Actually, that's true.
Trump gave a speech about 20 years ago where he said Epstein's a great guy.
He loves young women.
A lot of them are very young.
Nudge, nudge, wink, wink, laugh, laugh.
So, yeah, I think he's pro-crime and pro-criminal.
And I think he's soft on sex offenders.
Do you have any friends who are criminals?
Not that I know of.
Certainly not child sex offenders.
No.
Do you?
If it came, no, of course not.
If it came out tomorrow that one of your friends was a child sex offender, you'd stop
being friends with them?
Yes.
And then I'd go on TV and I would say, oh, look, Mr. Hassan was friends with this guy
10 years ago.
Therefore, he's pro-child sex trafficking.
What if Mr. Hassan said, I wish them well when they're on trial?
Wouldn't you have a go at me for that?
You wish your friend well on trial?
Yeah.
Child sex trafficker.
Would you be mad?
I wouldn't wish someone well, but that's your gotcha?
But Donald Trump did.
That's your gotcha?
It's a pretty big gotcha.
Yeah.
Pretty big gotcha.
Okay.
What you're really trying to do right now is you're trying to get back to Donald Trump
on a personal level.
What's his name?
What's his policy?
Oh, you want to talk policies?
Yes.
So when he left office in 2020, he left behind the highest murder rate for over a hundred
years.
He left behind the highest murder rate?
Yes.
That is the most bad faith claim you can possibly make.
No, no.
It's a fact from the CDC data.
And you know what?
Here's why it's bad faith.
Can I finish a sentence?
And then you can come back in.
You're just lying to people.
Donald Trump.
I'm lying?
Can I finish the sentence?
Donald Trump does not cause the murder rate.
Murder is a state level crime.
Oh, that's hilarious.
Gavin Newsom is more responsible for the murder rate than Donald Trump is.
That's hilarious.
Yes, because it's a state level law.
Everyone can see your partisanship.
No, I'll say Republicans are too.
State governors who are soft on crime are the ones that are responsible for murder rates.
Let me finish a sentence.
When Donald Trump left office in 2020, between 2019 and 2020, according to data from the
CDC, from the FBI, from Pew Research, the 30% increase in the murder rate between 2019
and 2020 was the single biggest jump in the murder rate since 1905.
So he's pro-crime and pro-criminal.
And who's doing the murdering?
Who's doing the murdering?
The murderers.
So aren't they responsible for the murder rate?
And who's doing the murdering?
The murderers.
So aren't they responsible for the murder rate?
Why did it go up on his watch?
He's very bad.
He's very bad at fighting crime for Republicans.
That's a real hard one to figure out.
We shut down the whole economy during COVID.
We told everyone they couldn't go out unless it was to violently protest.
We told people that if a cop tries to arrest you, that cop's probably gonna get charged
with murder.
No, I think the pandemic had a lot to do with it.
But the pandemic didn't finish in 2020.
Did he cause that?
What?
The pandemic didn't finish in 2020.
And yet you all...
And yet if we're gonna break the one about, you guys blamed Joe Biden for crime for years.
He is.
Joe Biden actively induces policies that are pro-crime.
I'm asking you for some...
So does Donald Trump...
Name the policy that's pro-crime.
I'll name one right now.
Please.
I asked you for like 10 minutes.
Please do that.
I'll name one right now.
No, you haven't.
Actually, you talked about California legislatures.
He pardoned violent criminals who then went on to commit other crimes.
You don't think releasing violent criminals is pro-crime?
I don't think it's...
I don't think it's pro-crime.
I've asked you for 10 minutes.
I'll name one right now.
Please do that.
No, you haven't.
Actually, you talked about California legislatures.
He pardoned violent criminals who then went on to commit other crimes.
That's not a policy.
You don't think releasing violent crimes into the community...
A pardon is a one time things.
What's his policy that he has pushed.
Do you know...
Name a law he has signed.
Hold on, a pardon is a one time thing.
It's a policy, it's not a one time thing.
That's like Jimmy Carter pardoned the draft doctors.
You guys may wanna dodge January 6th the pardons...
I'm not dodging that...
Then deal with it.
Did you agree with them?
Jimmy Carter pardoned the drafted doctors...
I don't support Jimmy Carter.
Do you support the pardoning of people who went on to be prosecuted for sexually abusing
a seven year old child, illegal gun possession, reckless homicide?
See, there's more bad things.
There's more bad things.
He didn't pardon someone for sexually abusing a child.
He pardoned someone for rebelling against a government that they believed had rigged
elections.
That's what he pardoned them for.
He didn't pardon them for sexual child abuse.
But they were criminals who committed those crimes.
He let them out.
So that means the crime rate goes up.
You say they're criminals because they did the crime, right?
Would you extend that to illegal immigrants, that they're all criminals because they committed
a crime?
I have a feeling your position is going to change.
No.
The Supreme Court...
We're going to talk about immigration.
Someone who's illegally entered the United States, not a criminal, but somebody who illegally
entered the Capitol is...
Not according to the Supreme Court.
Not according to the Supreme Court of the United States.
The Supreme Court has said that anyone who enters the United States illegally is not
a criminal.
What's the case site?
Can I get the case site?
We can jump to future claims.
We can jump to...
You want to get the case?
The case site, please.
You said the Supreme Court said...
The citation of the case.
Yes, that entering the United States illegally is not a crime.
Look it up.
Pause.
You've been voted out by the majority.